Which window will be most acceptable for
哪个窗口最能接受
an international business application to have scheduled downtime?
已安排停机时间的国际业务应用程序 ?
The answer is, the first Saturday of the month from 1:00-4:00 AM.
答案是 从上午 1:00-4:00 开始的第一个星期六
The things we want to consider here are,
我们想考虑的是
what is our user base,
我们的用户基地是什么
and when are they likely to be using our application?
什么时候他们会使用我们的应用呢 ?
Because we're talking about international customers,
因为我们说的是国际客户
we should be very careful when assuming thing about time zones.
我们在假设时区的时候应该很谨慎
However, since we're talking about a business application,
但是既然我们说的是商业应用
we can't assume things about the workweek versus the weekend.
我们不能假设工作周和周末的事